Hello Ajay, hello friend, let's
talk about ICICI Lombard. There has been a
decline of around 14% today
in ICICI Lombard, so we will discuss what to do and
what not to do.
Apart from this, if we talk about it, there is nutritious news in it,
Indian Excise Bottle tagged
IPL final approval, you could have seen Idea
Grand Final Loot General Insurance Business
Bharti AXA General Insurance Co. Ltd.
Debit General Insurance, if
you look for subscription and
if you talk about it, we
told you to subscribe to it here a long time ago and we had
talked about it, so here I had told you that you
can do it in it, it goes
up in a way, whether it goes up or
not, so if
you people were changing the momentum and you bought here, then there is
no need to panic right now, if the stock is there then there is
no need to book a loss at all
and if brother, you are planning to buy,
thinking of taking a new entry, then
again but we would like to wait, if it is
around 1450 or around 1500, then do
not take entry here  You can and if
you see this, it has happened a long time ago, since I was
making this channel, it has been happening very fast, so
these things are such that it is not that if you feel hungry then this
cannot happen, from here one and a half inch from here
onwards, first we
buy again in the upward direction, then we will
wait, if so then it is fine, otherwise it is okay,
we keep searching, we
start searching, when people are feeling scared,
people are afraid that how can I
do it here, then we also do it and when people do
profit booking there, when
brothers run to buy it, when there is a stock
fight, then whoever bought it would have booked 5 pockets in it at
that time, and so
this strat is fine, the rest is your wish, you
can ask for your money connected images, you
can also make your own, so 19 now subscribe to your channel
One News channel with this, you
should set it in the morning, friends,